Elizabeth Wolner

UX Designer & Product Engineer

Contact

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/elizabeth-wolner-6ba66255/ Portfolio: https://woln0037.github.io/Bootstrap-Site/index.html

Email: <u>elizabeth.wolner@gmail.com</u>

Mobile: 612-940-3488

About

Exceedingly curious Minneapolis-based UX Designer focused on customer satisfaction with experience in Engineering, Product Design, and a passion for Customer Service.

Skills

Technical: Figma; InVision; Visual Studio; GitHub; HTML/CSS; Office Suite; Adobe Suite UX/UI: User Research & Interviews; Wireframing; Prototyping; Site mapping; ADA Compliance

Projects

Target Corporation - Minneapolis, MN

UX Product Designer gig November 2022-Present (on top of my day job)

- Research & re-design part of the Same Day Delivery web/mobile experience with inputs from a cross-functional team of engineers, product owners, designers, etc.
- Skills: Figma: prototyping/wireframing; A/B testing, interpreting research data

University of Minnesota Bootcamp Case Studies - Minneapolis, MN

Government Agency Web & Mobile Redesign - Group Project

https://woln0037.github.io/Bootstrap-Site/case_study-cfia.html

- My role: Improve the navigation flow of the site and create design system components
- Skills: user research, user testing, card sorting, site mapping, mid/hi-fi prototyping

Pantry Pal Mobile App Design - Group Project

https://woln0037.github.io/Bootstrap-Site/case_study-pantry_pal.html

- My role: Use research and data to create empathy for the user & design prototype
- Skills: user research, journey mapping, storyboarding, user flow, low-fi prototyping

Travel Mobile App Design - Individual Project

https://woln0037.github.io/Bootstrap-Site/case_study-travel_app.html

- Designed a solution to help users plan travel in a post-pandemic world
- Skills: user persona, competitor analysis, guerilla user testing, wireframing, prototyping

Theater Site Redesign - Group Project

https://woln0037.github.io/Theater-Redesign/Theater/ | Presentation

- My role: Conduct user research, code the redesigned navigation in bootstrap/CSS
- Skills: user research, mood board, affinity diagram, prototyping, HTML, Bootstrap, CSS

Experience

Target Corporation - Minneapolis, MN

Product Engineer 2020-Present

^ | Associate Product Engineer 2016-2020

^ | Product Engineer Intern 2015-2016

- Lead technical development for Kitchen Tabletop products for the Hearth & Hand brand with a focus on continuous improvement and guest satisfaction
- Work on high-visibility projects with exclusive designer partners like Disney, Vineyard Vines, Levis, Tabitha Brown, and Joanna Gaines to ensure high product quality and to bring their visions to life
- Collaborate and manage relationships with a cross-functional team of vendor partners, designers, engineers, quality assurance specialists, sourcing partners, and buyers to connect the dots of the product development process.
- Drive \$124k in sales on average per year
- Frequently brought in on special business projects and have experience whiteboard and defining problems, then executing solutions

University of Minnesota - Minneapolis, MN

Volunteer Instructor - Product Design 2014-2022

- Lead a group of 6 students through the full product development process beginning with brainstorming and research, moving to concept development and user testing, and working through low, mid, and high-fidelity physical prototypes
- Troubleshoot student roadblocks and coach them towards solutions
- Grade student work and give feedback on performance throughout the course

Design Student Alumni Board Member/President 2016-2021

- Connect students and alumni by planning events
- Elected president after just 2 years of serving on the board & served from 2020-2021
- Recruited talent for both the Design in 7 and Dirty Laundry speaker series' with a focus on advocacy for a diverse lens

Bracketron - Edina, MN

Product Designer 2015-2016

- Ideated with leadership and the team to understand customer needs
- Developed packaging concepts for car mounts
- Used CAD software (Solidworks) daily to bring designs to life

Education

University of Minnesota - Minneapolis, MN

UX/UI Design Certificate BS Industrial & Systems Engineering 2022
BS Industrial & Systems Engineering 2011-2016 | product design/management focus